Welcome back.
-: Bienvenido de nuevo.
In this section, we're going to look
En esta seccin, vamos
at how you can run your Python programmes
a ver cmo puede ejecutar sus
without depending on PyCharm.
programas de Python sin depender de PyCharm.
Using PyCharm is great.
Usar PyCharm es genial.
It's a great tool, very simple,
Es una gran herramienta, muy simple,
but many times you'll want to run your Python programmes
pero muchas veces querrs ejecutar tus programas de
in a server on the internet, for example,
Python en un servidor en Internet, por ejemplo,
or you may want to share them with somebody else
o puedes querer compartirlos con
who doesn't have PyCharm.
alguien que no tenga PyCharm.
And in those cases, it can be useful to know
Y en esos casos, puede
how to run your applications without using it.
ser til saber cmo ejecutar sus aplicaciones sin usarlo.
In addition, we're also going to look
Adems, tambin vamos a ver
at how to structure your projects and their dependencies,
cmo estructurar sus proyectos y sus dependencias, las bibliotecas
any libraries you need
que necesita para que sea
so that it's a bit simpler to work
un poco ms simple trabajar
when you're doing many projects at once.
cuando hace muchos proyectos a la vez.
I'll see you on the next video.
Te ver en el prximo video.